# HARDIK MANGUKIYA

hardik.mangukiya.003@gmail.com +64225332568

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

Self-managed developer who likes to investigate and accept challenges and whose work experience is focused mostly on developing side front0end and Back-end. I would like to be one of key developers in a strong proactive "continuous delivery"-aware development team working on a project that will require the team to make long-term architectural decisions and master new frameworks.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### **MOST EXPERIENCED WITH:**

- <u>Skills</u>: SDLC, QA, C#, JavaScript/jQuery, SQL, HTML, Bootstrap, TDD, REST APIs, Entity Framework, .NET Framework and Core, ASP.NET MVC, Three-Tier Architecture, NuGet, using Google and Stack Overflow.
- Tools: Visual Studio, Postman, Asana, Jira, SVN.

#### **FAMILIAR WITH:**

- Skills: Sql procedures, CSS, Entity framework, LINQ, Asp.net core, using Google and Stack Overflow.
- Tools: Microsoft SQL server Management Studio, visual studio code.

#### **CERTIFICATION**

• IC Agile Certified (Agile Methodology)

#### **WORK HISTORY**

#### **Total IT Solution**

Auckland, New Zealand Apr 2019 – June 2019

#### **Technician - Intern**

- Maintain websites and Update every week.
- Understand customer queries, Maintain and support hardware to the customer.
- Processed, sorted, fixed, repaired, and imaged countless computers.
- Data Backup for Damaged HDD
- Setup monitoring and managing customized catalogs, reporting.
- Everyday CRM and Inventory update

# **Differenz System**

Surat, India Apr 2017 - Jun 2017

- Maintained, debugged, bug fixed, and extended existing ASP.NET MVC projects.
- Developed and design new websites, microservice from scratch and solo.
- Integrated with REST APIs as well as building REST based APIs.
- Participated in code reviews and demos in an Agile environment.
- Worked with the full stack from adding tables and store procedures in the SQL DB to server-side services and controllers in C# to the client-side views using HTML, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, and other JS libraries.

#### **Elaunch Infotech**

Surat, India Sep 2016 - Mar 2017

## Jr. Software Developer

Jr. Software Developer

- Data Visualization: Wrote SQL script for generate reports.
- Work on CRM and ERP system and make some modules for it.
- Worked on company's in-house project on both front end as well as business logic.
- Suggested and added a feature called Email notification in project.

# **QUALIFICATIONS**

# **United Institute of Technology**

Auckland, New Zealand Dec 2018

# **Graduate Diploma in Computing**

My major is Business Analyst, Papers include Project Planning, Internet and Website development, Manual/Automation Testing, Agile and Lean Software Development.

## **Babariya Institute of Technology**

Vadodara, India Jun 2016

# Bachelor's in computer science and Engineering

Founded and taught at the Specialist Hardware and Programming, I learnt about object-oriented programming, ERP system, and Software Database system.

#### **VISA STATUS**

I am on Post study open work visa holder at present. My visa will be expired on 12 Feb 2022.

# **REFEREES**

Available on request.